[
    {"question": "att vara", "answer": "var","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ha", "answer": "hade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att göra", "answer": "gjorde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att säga", "answer": "sa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att gå", "answer": "gick","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att komma", "answer": "kom","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att se", "answer": "såg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ta", "answer": "tog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ge", "answer": "gav","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att veta", "answer": "visste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att få", "answer": "fick","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vilja", "answer": "ville","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kunna", "answer": "kunde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att behöva", "answer": "behövde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tro", "answer": "trodde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tycka", "answer": "tyckte","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att känna", "answer": "kände","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att leva", "answer": "levde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dö", "answer": "dog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att skriva", "answer": "skrev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att läsa", "answer": "läste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tala", "answer": "talade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att höra", "answer": "hörde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att lyssna", "answer": "lyssnade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att förstå", "answer": "förstod","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att lära", "answer": "lärde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att fråga", "answer": "frågade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att svara", "answer": "svarade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att arbeta", "answer": "arbetade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att spela", "answer": "spelade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att springa", "answer": "sprang","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att simma", "answer": "simmade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att cykla", "answer": "cyklade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att köra", "answer": "körde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att flyga", "answer": "flög","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att resa", "answer": "reste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stanna", "answer": "stannade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att börja", "answer": "började","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sluta", "answer": "slutade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att öppna", "answer": "öppnade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stänga", "answer": "stängde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sitta", "answer": "satt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stå", "answer": "stod","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ligga", "answer": "låg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sova", "answer": "sov","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vakna", "answer": "vaknade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att äta", "answer": "åt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dricka", "answer": "drack","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att laga", "answer": "lagade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att baka", "answer": "bakade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att köpa", "answer": "köpte","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sälja", "answer": "sålde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att betala", "answer": "betalade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att fånga", "answer": "fångade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kasta", "answer": "kastade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att slå", "answer": "slog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sparka", "answer": "sparkade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att gråta", "answer": "grät","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att skratta", "answer": "skrattade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att le", "answer": "log","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kyssa", "answer": "kysste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att krama", "answer": "kramade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att hata", "answer": "hatade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att älska", "answer": "älskade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att hoppas", "answer": "hoppades","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att drömma", "answer": "drömde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tänka", "answer": "tänkte","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att minnas", "answer": "mindes","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att glömma", "answer": "glömde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vinna", "answer": "vann","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att förlora", "answer": "förlorade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kämpa", "answer": "kämpade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att segra", "answer": "segrade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att bygga", "answer": "byggde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att riva", "answer": "rev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att måla", "answer": "målade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att reparera", "answer": "reparerade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tvätta", "answer": "tvättade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att städa", "answer": "städade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dammsuga", "answer": "dammsög","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stryka", "answer": "strök","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sy", "answer": "sydde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sticka", "answer": "stickade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att virka", "answer": "virkade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att läsa", "answer": "läste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att skriva", "answer": "skrev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att rita", "answer": "ritade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att måla", "answer": "målade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sjunga", "answer": "sjöng","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dansa", "answer": "dansade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att spela", "answer": "spelade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att lyssna", "answer": "lyssnade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att titta", "answer": "tittade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att se", "answer": "såg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att höra", "answer": "hörde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att känna", "answer": "kände","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att smaka", "answer": "smakade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att lukta", "answer": "luktade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att röra", "answer": "rörde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att klappa", "answer": "klappade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att slå", "answer": "slog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sparka", "answer": "sparkade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kasta", "answer": "kastade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att fånga", "answer": "fångade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att hoppa", "answer": "hoppade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att springa", "answer": "sprang","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att gå", "answer": "gick","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att cykla", "answer": "cyklade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att simma", "answer": "simmade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att flyga", "answer": "flög","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att köra", "answer": "körde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att resa", "answer": "reste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stanna", "answer": "stannade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att börja", "answer": "började","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sluta", "answer": "slutade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att öppna", "answer": "öppnade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stänga", "answer": "stängde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sitta", "answer": "satt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stå", "answer": "stod","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ligga", "answer": "låg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sova", "answer": "sov","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vakna", "answer": "vaknade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att äta", "answer": "åt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dricka", "answer": "drack","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att laga", "answer": "lagade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att baka", "answer": "bakade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att köpa", "answer": "köpte","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vara", "answer": "var","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ha", "answer": "hade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att göra", "answer": "gjorde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att säga", "answer": "sa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att gå", "answer": "gick","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att komma", "answer": "kom","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att se", "answer": "såg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ta", "answer": "tog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ge", "answer": "gav","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att veta", "answer": "visste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att få", "answer": "fick","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vilja", "answer": "ville","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kunna", "answer": "kunde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att behöva", "answer": "behövde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tro", "answer": "trodde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tycka", "answer": "tyckte","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att känna", "answer": "kände","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att leva", "answer": "levde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dö", "answer": "dog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att skriva", "answer": "skrev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att läsa", "answer": "läste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tala", "answer": "talade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att höra", "answer": "hörde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att lyssna", "answer": "lyssnade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att förstå", "answer": "förstod","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att lära", "answer": "lärde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att fråga", "answer": "frågade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att svara", "answer": "svarade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att arbeta", "answer": "arbetade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att spela", "answer": "spelade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att springa", "answer": "sprang","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att simma", "answer": "simmade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att cykla", "answer": "cyklade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att köra", "answer": "körde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att flyga", "answer": "flög","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att resa", "answer": "reste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stanna", "answer": "stannade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att börja", "answer": "började","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sluta", "answer": "slutade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att öppna", "answer": "öppnade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stänga", "answer": "stängde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sitta", "answer": "satt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stå", "answer": "stod","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ligga", "answer": "låg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sova", "answer": "sov","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vakna", "answer": "vaknade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att äta", "answer": "åt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dricka", "answer": "drack","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att laga", "answer": "lagade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att baka", "answer": "bakade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att köpa", "answer": "köpte","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sälja", "answer": "sålde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att betala", "answer": "betalade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att fånga", "answer": "fångade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kasta", "answer": "kastade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att slå", "answer": "slog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sparka", "answer": "sparkade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att gråta", "answer": "grät","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att skratta", "answer": "skrattade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att le", "answer": "log","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kyssa", "answer": "kysste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att krama", "answer": "kramade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att hata", "answer": "hatade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att älska", "answer": "älskade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att hoppas", "answer": "hoppades","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att drömma", "answer": "drömde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tänka", "answer": "tänkte","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att minnas", "answer": "mindes","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att glömma", "answer": "glömde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vinna", "answer": "vann","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att förlora", "answer": "förlorade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kämpa", "answer": "kämpade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att segra", "answer": "segrade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att bygga", "answer": "byggde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att riva", "answer": "rev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att måla", "answer": "målade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att reparera", "answer": "reparerade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att tvätta", "answer": "tvättade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att städa", "answer": "städade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dammsuga", "answer": "dammsög","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stryka", "answer": "strök","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sy", "answer": "sydde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sticka", "answer": "stickade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att virka", "answer": "virkade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att läsa", "answer": "läste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att skriva", "answer": "skrev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att rita", "answer": "ritade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att måla", "answer": "målade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sjunga", "answer": "sjöng","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dansa", "answer": "dansade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att spela", "answer": "spelade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att lyssna", "answer": "lyssnade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att titta", "answer": "tittade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att se", "answer": "såg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att höra", "answer": "hörde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att känna", "answer": "kände","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att smaka", "answer": "smakade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att lukta", "answer": "luktade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att röra", "answer": "rörde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att klappa", "answer": "klappade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att slå", "answer": "slog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sparka", "answer": "sparkade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att kasta", "answer": "kastade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att fånga", "answer": "fångade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att hoppa", "answer": "hoppade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att springa", "answer": "sprang","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att gå", "answer": "gick","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att cykla", "answer": "cyklade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att simma", "answer": "simmade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att flyga", "answer": "flög","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att köra", "answer": "körde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att resa", "answer": "reste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stanna", "answer": "stannade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att börja", "answer": "började","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sluta", "answer": "slutade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att öppna", "answer": "öppnade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stänga", "answer": "stängde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sitta", "answer": "satt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att stå", "answer": "stod","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att ligga", "answer": "låg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att sova", "answer": "sov","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att vakna", "answer": "vaknade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att äta", "answer": "åt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att dricka", "answer": "drack","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att laga", "answer": "lagade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att baka", "answer": "bakade","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "att köpa", "answer": "köpte","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"}
]